http://www.humbersidescouts.org.uk/privacy-policy

Website Privacy Policy
Information collection and use
We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed on this page.
We may collect basic personal information from you, in order to keep you informed with information, at your request. At any time, you can request to be removed from our contact database, and you will not hear from us again.
Secure storage
All of our data is stored with our web host. Only authorised members of staff who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We will not, under any circumstances, share with any third party individual IP addresses, email addresses, personal contact details or other information collected through this website or related statistic tracking systems. If information sharing is required for the purposes of this or any other event, you will be given immediate notice.
External links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Data protection
As we are not classed as a “data controller”, we do not have to notify the Information Commissioner about the information we collect or our practices. Please note however, that we comply meticulously with the eight principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 and understand best practice for managing information.
Questions
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can contact us.
Galleryview
© Humberside Scouts 2020.
An indicoll website
Privacy PolicyCookie PolicyAccessibilityDisclaimer
